iprental.com 2009-06-19

# IP Rental - Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy IPRental.com

Please note that the practices of IPRental, its affiliates, and agents ("IPRental"), with respect to data collected and used by IPRental in connection with this website and all other websites of IPRental with authorized links to this policy (collectively, the “Site”) and IPRental products and services available or enabled via the Site (“Products and Services”), are governed by this online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) as amended from time to time, and not the privacy policy in effect at the time the data was collected. This Privacy Policy does not apply to those IPRental sites, products and services that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that have their own privacy statements. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and the Products and Services enabled by the Site and follow the procedure described in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences." This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities, websites other than the Site, or products and services not available or enabled via the Site, except as expressly set forth in the section entitled "Data not collected on this Site." To the extent that any terms of the Privacy Policy conflict with the terms of an existing written (including electronic) agreement between you and IPRental regarding the use of specific areas of the Site or specific Products and Services (including Product- and Service-specific licenses, terms of use, or privacy disclosures) (collectively, “Product Agreements”), the terms of the Product Agreements shall govern. IPRental adheres to the European Union Safe Harbor principles as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information covered by the Privacy Policy from the European Union. The Site and the Products and Services are intended for adult audiences, and IPRental does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. 

## Changes in Privacy Policy

All personal information ("personal information" is defined as any information that identifies or can be used to identify the person to whom such information pertains) that we collect and maintain will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from time to time. IPRental may change the Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion and will provide notice of all changes in the Privacy Policy through indications on this Privacy Policy and in the footer of the web pages with authorized links to this Privacy Policy. If as the result of such changes you want to alter the ways in which IPRental is allowed to use your personal information, you can do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences.” You will be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to the Privacy Policy after such notice has been posted with the following exception: if at the time you provide personal information to IPRental you limit how such information will be used to communicate with you, either by IPRental or by third parties, IPRental will not change your preference in this regard without your express consent. However, if IPRental sells assets (or the assets of a division or subsidiary) to another entity, or IPRental (or a division or subsidiary) is acquired by or merged with another entity, you agree that IPRental may provide to such entity customer information that is related to that part of our business that was sold to or merged with the other entity without obtaining your further consent. IPRental will provide notice of such asset sales, acquisitions, or mergers on this Site..

## Entities collecting personal information

Personal information on this Site is collected on behalf of IPRental by IPRental, who is responsible for this Site. IPRental’s address is: Silver Group International Corporation, Dorado Mall Building, First floor, suites 26 & 27, Panama City, Rep. of Panama. The Site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided to the contrary, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site. That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.

## Updating your personal information and privacy preferences

You have the right to access, correct and delete inaccuracies in your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Registration Information (as defined in the section entitled "Protection of your personal information"), this may be accomplished by logging in to your account on the relevant IPRental website, where you can typically view and make changes to your personal information. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional communications) by emailing IPRental at [info@iprental.com](mailto:info@iprental.com).

## Collection of personal information

As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online or hosted Products and Services, IPRental may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and submitting a form. It is optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, IPRental may ask that you provide certain personal information (as well as certain non-personal information that may be tied to personal information), such as your first and last name, mailing address (including ZIP code), country of residence, e-mail address, employer, job title and department, and telephone and facsimile numbers,. When ordering Products and Services via the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number and billing and shipping information. Depending upon the activity, some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity. Similarly, if you wish to delete your information (pursuant to the mechanism set forth in “Updating your personal information and privacy preferences”) that is mandatory, you will no longer be able to engage in that particular activity.

IPRental does not log browsing data or history, does not track cookies, nor IP addresses or websites you have visited. IPRental's binary application does not contain any Adware or Spyware. 

When you use the Site and the Products and Services, IPRental may also collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use of the Site and the Products and Services. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, referring or exit webpages, click patterns, Session ID (a unique identifier assigned to the browser in connection to the Site), and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. IPRental also uses such information to measure traffic patterns on the Site and usage of the Products and Services. We do not match such information with personal information held about you by IPRental unless we have your consent, except as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

By using this Site and the Products and Services, you agree and acknowledge that personal information collected through the Site or in connection with the Products and Services may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world in which IPRental maintains offices, including the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by trusted third party vendors or agents of IPRental such as credit card processors, shipping agents, web hosting providers, mail and email service providers and web analytic providers, to help facilitate IPRental in providing certain functions. Another instance where this could occur is in conjunction with framed pages in which the URL for the pages is not visible, and the pages are hosted for IPRental by such third party vendors. For example, on the sign up pages for some newsletters, the pages may be hosted by a third party vendor, but appear to be IPRental.com pages and they are therefore governed by this Privacy Policy. Personal information may be shared with these providers to fulfill the service. Such third parties are bound by contract with IPRental not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.

## How your personal information is used

IPRental collects a minimal amount of information from its users, and intends to maintain the highest level of security and anonymity. IPRental will NEVER under any circumstances sell, share, or otherwise release your data to any third parties, and IPRental will not release your data to any law enforcement agencies without a subpoena or other applicable court order.

IPRental may use aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for improving the Site and the Products and Services, providing more relevant experiences to our customers and for statistical analysis.

## Your choices with respect to personal information

IPRental recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on the Site and in connection with the Products and Services. IPRental will respect your legal rights regarding access to, and correction and deletion of, your personal information. IPRental may communicate information to you regarding products, services, and special offers available from IPRental unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such communications are prohibited by law, although in such cases we may find it necessary to continue to communicate with you regarding your use of the Site and the Products and Services. 

There are other instances in which IPRental may divulge your personal information, such as when required by law, regulation, or litigation. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance.

## Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the Site or of the Products and Services is classified as Registration Information. Registration Information is protected in several ways. Access by you to your Registration Information is available through a password and unique customer ID selected by you. This password is encrypted. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. In addition, your Registration Information resides on secure servers that only selected IPRental personnel and contractors have access to via password. IPRental encrypts your personal information as it is transferred to IPRental and thereby strives to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing such information.

Personal information that you provide that does not constitute Registration Information also resides on secure servers and is accessible only to selected IPRental personnel and contractors via password. Since this information is not accessible online by you, you will not be asked to select a password in order to view or modify such information.

## Tracking, use of cookies, web beacons and similar devices

On the IPRental.com website we keep track of cookies for “my account” and payment processing, however the actual IPRental application does not track cookies, browsing histories, or store ANY cookie data, in fact when the IP is released and renewed IPRental application will remove the cookies which were locally stored in IE 6, 7, and 8 for all websites.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies, and most Products and Services that include similar devices are typically initially activated to collect data. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. (For some web pages that require an authorization, cookies are not optional. Users choosing not to accept cookies or similar devices will probably not be able to access those pages or the related Products and Services.) Information about non-cookie tracking devices and their features, including disabling options, are contained in the information materials provided with such Products and Services or on Site pages relating to such Products and Services.

## Privacy complaints

IPRental takes its users' privacy concerns seriously. If you believe that IPRental has not complied with this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information, you may write to the IPRental Privacy Officer at [info@iprental.com](mailto:info@iprental.com).

In your email, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly.
